

Personal

Name Mohamed M. Hassan

Address An der Weidigmühle 10 07743 Jena

Phone number +4917687532227

Email moatyiv@gmail.com

Date of birth 29-11-1997

Nationality Egyptian

Website http://8bitjunky.com

Languages

English Fluent
German Fluent
Arabic Native

Mohamed M. Hassan

I am a motivated, hardworking, ambitious bachelor student with a strong background in mathematics, Physics, Programming, and soft engineering skills such as design, testing, and problem analysis.

I am looking forward to using my technical skills in a challenging work environment and to be a helpful member of the

Company. where I develop myself further and exchange Expertise with my work colleagues

Education and Qualifications

Bachelor of Engineering

Oct 2017 - Present

Ernst-Abbe-Hochschule Jena, Jena, Germany

Studying Electrical and Computer Engineering with focus on Electronics and Embedded Systems. this includes but not limited to:

- Working with Microcontrollers
- Running a Real-time Operating System on micro chips
- FPGA with VHDL

Work experience

Plug-in Developer and Freelancer

2016 - 2018

Freelancer, Jena

Worked as a Plugin developer for the Unity Game Engine, creating 2 successful Plugins. on parallel I've worked as a Gameplay Programmer for a game studio in the UK to create a game Prototype

Full-stack developer

Feb 2019 - Aug 2019

Serimed GmbH, Jena

Created a Backend C# .NET Server that optimizes Serimed's internal work pipeline, controlled by a colorful AngularJs Frontend for the Serimed Admins as well as their Customers.

Embedded Software Developer

Aug 2019 - Present

Navimatix GmbH, Jena

Worked briefly on Navimatix's own Uni2Cast Project for IoT devices, before switching to running Zephyr (a RTOS) on custom-made Board and writing Drivers for custom modules, for a current on-going Project.

Skills

C/C++	
C# Frameworks (WPF, ASP.NET)	
Android App Development (Java and Native)	
Web Dev. (Springboot, AngularJs, HTML, JS)	
3D Game Development	
Python	
VHDL	